From the library window of the library, enter the basic pants file.
After selecting the rectangle tool, click on the 2D window, you can input specific values ​​in the window.
Press Ctrl D to create a symmetrical version.
Show the arrangement point Shift F and arrange the belt plate.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the belt.
You can change its position by changing the various arrangement values ​​in the attribute editor.
We need to ensure that the belt curve is in line with the human body curve.
By contrast, you can see that the belt curve is in line with the human body curve.
The front of the pants is lower than the front of the belt.
Add some curve points to draw a curve and modify the angle to a right angle.
Press Ctrl D and move the point, move it along the curve to shorten the length of the upper and lower eyes.
After simulation, you will see a belt that is more suitable for the body.
Freeze the belt plate and use the free sewing tool to sew the plate.
After creating the first seam line, you can press Shift D and continue to click on the line.
Select the multi-line seam line to be sewn.
Activate the belt plate and simulate.
Select the edit seam line tool, then select the line in the back of the plate, and select the merge in the menu in the right-hand corner.
Select the merge in the menu in the right-hand corner.
For belt application stitch, the stitch can maintain the shape of the plate in the 2D window and is not easy to slide in the 2D window.
In the library in the acceptable window, we can fold the hem of the pants and put them on the virtual model.
Move the bottom of the pants to shorten the length of the pants.
In the 3D window, freeze the belt plate.
Since the belt is frozen, the pants will shrink upward after the application mirror shrink.
Now we can make the foot plate.
Select the rectangle and click on the 2D window, then click on the window to enter the specific value.
Press CTRL D to create a symmetrical plate.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the side of the foot plate.
You can drag the plate to adjust the position of the foot.
Applied to the foot plate, it can keep its shape unchanged and reduce the sliding of other plates.
Reducing the scale can increase the detail of the clothing, which helps to check whether the clothing is integrated.
You can adjust the size of the foot plate.
Use the free sewing tool to sew the foot plate to the pants plate.
After creating the first seam line, you can press the SHIFT key and click on all the seams.
The seam line will be reduced to 100%.
At this time, due to the length of the plate, the fold will be made.
When moving the line, press the right mouse button to enter the specific value in the window.
You can adjust the length of the pants to control the fold.
At this time, the fold will be reduced to 100%.
To remove the symmetrical layer of the waist.
To set the proportion of the elastic application on the outside line of the plate of the upper and lower two sides as 100.
This step will maintain the length of the line.
The plate will not be transformed by the impact of the seam line.
Select the waist belt line and select the inner line of the curve line
For the middle line, apply the same 100 proportion of elasticity
To fix the waist belt position, you can press the W key and click on the clothing to add a fixed needle
Select the waist belt and select the outer curve line
Cancel the stickiness and elasticity of the curve line on the plate
And choose to remove the joint and cancel the joint of the inner and outer layers
Double-click to select the center point of the frame and activate the center point
So that the center can be loosened on the plate
We can delete the sewing line that was automatically created by the Cologne layer
And re-select the sewing plate through the free sewing tool
In this case, let's add a linked line so that it can be continuously tailored
Everybody can see how much it has been reduced
After that, we can freeze the pants plate and the waist belt plate.
For smaller plates, we can reduce the particle diameter to get more detailed results.
For the ankle plate, we can use 100% elasticity to keep its length unchanged.
Select the ankle plate and select the outer layer of the clavicle in the menu bar on the right.
After removing the joint of the ankle plate on the clavicle, we can cancel the elastic and banding applications.
When the two corresponding plates have no joint relationship,
we can remove the joint for them.
The joint is used to match the joint of the ankle plate and the banding line.
Remove a whole circle of the joint generated by the clavicle layer,
and use the banding tool to re-create the banding line to match the joint.
After selecting the joint, drag the selection box to widen the joint.
When the outer layer is larger than the inner layer,
due to the different sizes, the joint on the larger joint will be narrowed.
The joint on the smaller joint will be narrowed.
We can use the increase of the outer layer of the clavicle to create the same effect.
And reducing the joint diameter of the joint can make the effect more obvious.
Next, let's create the pocket.
In the 3D window, select the 3D panel tool.
Click on the panel to create a line.
Press CTRL and click to create a curve point.
Select the 3D panel tool and select the line drawn on the pants panel.
Then in the menu in the right-hand corner,
you can select the cut and sew under the symmetrical column.
Select the pocket panel's panel line.
Then in the menu in the right-hand corner,
select the panel line expansion and select Extend as the side angle.
Once you're done creating had the panel as you see,
we use the free sewing tool to sew up the part that was extended in the pocket.
Don't forget to copy the adjustment of the agreed line,
and precision
and then conflict with other versions.
Use the tool to modify the curve of the version.
Select the pants version and select the Cron from the outside in the menu bar on the right.
Unlock the link and set the left and right symmetry of the original version of the Cron.
Increase the aspect ratio and the aspect ratio of the tail.
To make the outer version of the Cron look bigger than the inner version.
After reducing the particle diameter, the spine will be more detailed and smooth.
In the material file folder in the library in the drawing box, there is a fabric folder.
We can see the pre-set fabric in Marvelous Designer.
We can use the knit cotton jersey to wear the version.
Add a layer mask to the work area, you can learn how to make it through the previous video.
Arrange the panels in the 2D window.
Select the face mask and set the layer level to 1.
We need to freeze the pants panels, this will help us prevent the wear and tear from becoming unstable.
After the face mask is worn to the outside of the pants, activate all panels and set the layer level to 0.
Then simulate, let the panels naturally wear on the model.
Open the project page, to see if the model has been changed.
To see the model, select the model, select the model, select the model, and click in the control panel.
Now, you can see, the model has changed, and it creates the new 3D model.
Now you can see, the model is now different from normal.
Now you can see, the model has changed, and it creates new 3D models.
Then, let's work on the model, the model is now in the model mode.